https://www.htd.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Javascript is disabled on your browser.
To view this site, you must enable JavaScript or upgrade to a JavaScript-capable browser.
972-312-9900 M-F 8a-6p CST
Products and Support For A Successful Home Audio ProjectManufacturing and Selling Direct Since 1999M-F 8a-6p CST   972-312-9900   Toll Free 866-483-2834
Login
0 items
Your cart is empty
Go
Home
Products SpeakersTraditional Cabinet SpeakersIn-Ceiling / In-Wall SpeakersOn-wall / SoundbarsOutdoor SpeakersPowered SubwoofersAmplifiers2-Channel (Stereo)Multi-ChannelSubwoofer AmplifiersWhole-House AudioMid-Level (MC/MCA) SystemAdvanced (Lync) SystemSystems Without KeypadsAlexa CentricHybrid Wireless SystemBasic SystemHTD MC App - NEW!HTD Lync App - NEW!Whole-House AccessoriesHelp Me ChooseCables & AccessoriesAlexa Ceiling MountsPre-Construction Speaker BracketsSpeaker Stands and Mounting BracketsSpeaker CablesCable Connectors and Wall PlatesLine Level Gain BoostersDACs (Digital to Analog Converters)Audio BalunsVolume ControlsIR DistributionHTD OutletB-StockDiscontinuedShipping *Free $500+Risk Free In-Home Trial30 Day GuaranteeWarrantyReturn PolicyShipping & TaxCustomer Reviews Expert Support OverviewUpload Your PlansHow-To VideosAudio FAQDownloadsContact UsAbout UsAbout UsOur PoliciesContact UsNow Hiring   Fair shipping: *FedEx Ground $10-25; FREE over $500       |      Fast shipping: most orders received by 2pm CST ship the same business day      |      More Info  *Continental USA & CanadaFixed Rate ShippingTotalFedEx GroundOther DeliveryOrder*USA†CanadaMethods$0 - $99$10$25Actual FedEx Rate$100 - $299$15$30Actual FedEx Rate$300 - $499$25$40Actual FedEx Rate$500+FREE$50Actual FedEx RateUSA Shipping TimesCanada Shipping Times*FedEx Ground capped rates are not available for shipments to Hawaii, Alaska, Puerto Rico and The Virgin Islands.†As a convenience to our Canadian customers, we also collect a prepaid, all-inclusive amount to cover customs clearance, duty, and other government fees. You are not contacted during transit and pay nothing upon delivery. This amount, typically 12-17% depending on province, is clearly displayed during checkout before your order is placed. Please note that these charges are not refundable as part of our 30-day guarantee. To maintain low shipping rates to our customers, Canadian orders are consolidated to ship out on Tuesdays and Fridays. Full Details: Shipping & Tax   30 Day Guarantee   Warranty   Return PolicyFast & Fair ShippingContinental USA & CanadaFixed Rate ShippingTotalFedEx GroundOther DeliveryOrder*USA†CanadaMethods$0 - $99$10$25Actual FedEx Rate$100 - $299$15$30Actual FedEx Rate$300 - $499$25$40Actual FedEx Rate$500+FREE$50Actual FedEx RateUSA Shipping TimesCanada Shipping Times*FedEx Ground capped rates are not available for shipments to Hawaii, Alaska, Puerto Rico and The Virgin Islands.†As a convenience to our Canadian customers, we also collect a prepaid, all-inclusive amount to cover customs clearance, duty, and other government fees. You are not contacted during transit and pay nothing upon delivery. This amount, typically 14-19% depending on province, is clearly displayed during checkout before your order is placed. Please note that these charges are not refundable as part of our 30-day guarantee. To maintain low shipping rates to our customers, Canadian orders are consolidated to ship out on Tuesdays and Fridays. Click to get full details on Shipping and Tax
Home
Privacy Policy
Our Privacy PolicyWe respect your privacy! Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed by Home Theater Direct. Any information you provide will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways in which you have not consented.Comments supplied directly to Home Theater Direct or indirectly through a third-party review service, may be displayed at our web site or otherwise used or printed in conjunction with the promotion of our site, brand name, or products. The exact identity of the source of such comments is kept confidential, with only the source's alias or first name and first initial of last name, and hometown published.As you browse www.HTD.com cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can better understand what you are interested in and save your shopping cart contents for you. Our advertising partners enable us to present you with specific ads on other sites based on your previous interaction with www.HTD.com. The techniques employed do not collect any personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number.
Customer Reviews30 Day GuaranteeWarrantyShipping & TaxPrivacy PolicyWork HereMy AccountAbout usReturn PolicyContact Us972-312-9900toll free: 1-866-483-2834Email us© 2019 Home Theater Direct, Inc.1000 Shiloh Rd. #100, Plano, TX 750741-866-HTD-AUDIO (866-483-2834)
